Guide to the Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records, 1982-1993.
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records
- Interfaith Action for Economic Jusice "US Security Assistance to Overdeveloping Countries", 1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Senate Base Rights and Burden sharing, 1988-03-21 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- US Congress hearing 1988 House Human Rights Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- House Special Operation Panel, 1988-03-02 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- La Rocque Testamony, 1988-04-19 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- House Select Committee on Hunger, 1988-06-16 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- US Congressional Hearing House Appropriations, 1988-03-30 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- US Congress - April 1988 Human Rights Caucus, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- US Congressional Hearing Bills: Senate Appropriations, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Committee on Justice and Human Rights Report on Vigilante Groups 1987, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- 23/9/87 "Low Intensity Conflict - The Nature of the Threat", 1987-09-23 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Senate East Asian and Pacific Affairs MRGS 10/8/97, 1997-10-08 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- House-Asian and Pacific Affairs Hearing 12/2/87, 1987-12-02 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Solarz Subcommittee 9/10/87, 1987-09-10 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Congress 1985, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Philippine Embassy Protest 1985, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Senate Intelligence Committee - Staff Report, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 50)
- US Congressional Testimonies - House Asia and Pacific Subcommittee 3/17/87, 1987-03-17 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Walden's Classic Memo 6/27/86, 1986-27-06 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Misc. Congress, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 1)
- HR Work/Networking, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 2)
- PHRL/Advocacy, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 3)
- MAI, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Congress, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 5)
- PHRL - Minutes and Mailings - PAZ, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 6)
- NECP Lobbying Efforts 1991, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- PHRL - Minutes and Mailings - 1991, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Congress: Members/info/issues, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Sept. 1991 Bases Letters/Article to Congress, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Church Leaders-Sign on Letter to Foreign Ops and For. Rel. 1991, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- PHRL - Minutes and Mailings - 1990, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Dear Colleague Letter - 1990 Legislative Advoc. 1989, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- State Department, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Report to Committee on Appropriations US Senate - US State Department, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Testimonies-July 25, 1990, 1990-07-25 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Testimonies-House Committee on Foreign Affairs, Subcommittee on Pacific Affairs 1/30/90, 1990-01-30 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- 1990 Congressional Visit Report Form, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Kalaw Testimony - 26 Sept 1990 sub-comm on HR and International Orignations Committee on Foreign affiars - House of Rep., 1990-09-26 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Correspondence with Congress 1989, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- 2/7/89 Subcommittee on For. Ops House Comm. On Appropriations, 1989-02-07 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Washington Institute for Values in Public Policy/"Reg. Security for Asia and the Pacific" 2/9/89, 1989-02-09 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Aquino Campaign, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Jesse Jackson, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 24)
- August 21, 1985 Events, 1985-08-21 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- September 1985 Events, 1985-09 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Philippines Information Packet Permit for Rally, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 27)
- PREPARE (Impact) Project, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Sr. Margot Lloren, Jan-Feb. 86, 1986-01-1986-02 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Itinerations and Programs, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Phil. Human Rights Lobby Group, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Testimonies 1988, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- 2nd National Lobby Day May 2nd, 1985, 1985-05-02 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Philippines Press Information Packet, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Church Statement on HR in Phils., Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Philippines Duplicates of Petitions 1985 Congress Campaign, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Congress Alerts, Date unknown (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Testimonies 1987, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Congress Campaign 1985, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- National Movement for Civil Liberties, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Kilusang Magbubukid ng Pilipinas, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 2)
- FARDEC (Central Visayas Farmers Development Center), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 3)
- CPAR, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 4)
- BAYAN, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Indigenous Flinipinos, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Cordillera People's Alliance, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Cordillera Consultation and Research, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Center for development Programs in the Cordillera, Inc, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Young Christian Workers, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Tuluyan, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 11)
- SAMIN, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Pentecost, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Philippine Peasant Institute, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 14)
- National Org. of Women Religious in the Philippines (NOWRP), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 15)
- KADENA, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Kairos, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Jesuits, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Initiative for International Dialogue, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 19)
- FIDES, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Clergy Laity Formation Program, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Anti-Bases Coalition, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 22)
- AKKAPKA, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 23)
- New York City, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 24)
- WOMEN Materials, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Asia solidarity Groups, Contacts, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Friends of the Filipino People, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Philippine Study Group of Minnesota (PSGM), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Philippine Labor Alert, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Alliance for Philippine Concerns, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 30)
- CAMD/PSN, CTF, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Task Force on the Philippines - J and P Com. Honolulu Diocese, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 32)
- PAX CHRISTI, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Network, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Maryknoll, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Philadelphia, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Washington Group - Potentials, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Norfolk, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 38)
- TULAY (LA-based support group), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Chicago, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Canada, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Church Network on the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Key contact Mailing List, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Nationalist Alliance for Justice, Freedom and Democracy, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Ecumenical Comm. For Displaced Families and Communities (ECDFC), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Ecumenical Campus Ministry Northern Luzon, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 46)
- BAYAN, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Salasayan Peach Corp, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Base Conversion News ctr. For Economic Conversion, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Children of War, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Partido ng Bayan PNB/ANP, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 51)
- American Ass'n for the Advancement of Science, etc Fact-Finding M'sn 1983, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- American Ass'n for the Advancement of Science, etc Fact-Finding M'sn 1983, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- American Committees for Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Visayas Monitor 1987 (issues processed), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Mindanao Human Rights Monitor 86-87 (issues processed), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Phil Human Rights UPDATE 1987 (issues processed), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Phil Human Rights UPDATE 1986 (issues processed), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Phil Human Rights UPDATE 1985 (issues processed), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Amnesty International-85, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- International Association of Democratic Lawyers, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Political Detainees UPDATE 1980-1981 (issues processed), 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- TFD Update 1982 (issues processed), 1982 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- TFD Political Detainees Update Quarterly Report (issues processed), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 60)
- TFD Update 1983 (issues processed), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- TFD Update 1984 (issues processed), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- TFD Update 1985 (issues processed), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- TFD Update 1985 Extra Copies (issues processed), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Pahatid Kapatid (issues processed), Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Ecumenical Movement for Justice and Peace, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 65)
- United Church of Christ in the Phils Human Rights Desk, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 66)
- HR Report - Trends and Analysis 1984 (issues processed), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Philippine Human Rights Luzon, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 68)
- MINDANAO, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Human Rights-Visayas, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Fact Finding Missions, Date unknown (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Pagasa Newsletter (Issues processed), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Hudyat ng Usok (Samahang Pinoy Int'l) (Issues processed), Date unknown (Box 11)
- CPJ Update (Issues processed), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Australian Solidarity Groups, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Asian Publication, Date unknown (Box 11)
- RESIST, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Hamletting in Cagayan Valley, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Original of hand-outs/reprints, etc, Date unknown (Box 11)
- House foreign affairs, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Leaflet/Brochure/Reductions/Other - Designs - (Dry transfers), Date unknown (Box 11)
- CALC, Date unknown (Box 11)
- CICM - Missionhurst, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Task force on Militarization in Asia and the Pacific, Date unknown (Box 11)
- East Asia/Pacific Office National Council of Churches of Christ, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Churches and REL in LS, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Church Related - ICUIS, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Mary Knoll Justice and Peace, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Board of Global Ministries United Methodist Church, Date unknown (Box 11)
- EPIC, Date unknown (Box 11)
- St. Louis Talk, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Talks, Speaking Engagements, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Blank Schedule Forms, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Originals of Forms, Date unknown (Box 11)
- American Association for the Advancement of Science, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Asia Watch, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Asia Pacific Working Group, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Amnesty International, Date unknown (Box 11)
- American Christians for the Abolition of Torture (ACAT), Date unknown (Box 11)
- American Friends Service Committee, Date unknown (Box 11)
- American Committees for Human Rights (Jonathan Fine), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Campaign for Political Rights, Date unknown (Box 11)
- CNFMP, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Center of Concern (Sr. Maria Riley/Joe Holland), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Center for Development Policy (US-Asia Relations Commission), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Center for the Progress of Peoples, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Center for National Security Studies, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Committee to Protect Journalists, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Human Rights Internet, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Lawyers Committee for International Human rights (LCIHR), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Institute for Policy Studies (IPS), Date unknown (Box 11)
- North American Coalition for Human Rights in Korea, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Nuclear Free Pacific, Date unknown (Box 11)
- PAWG (Pacific-Asia Working Group), Date unknown (Box 11)
- Quixote Center (Maureen Fiendler, and others), Date unknown (Box 11)
- United Nations Human Rights Commission, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Cartoon Clips, Date unknown (Box 11)
- Statement of Receipts and Disbursements (1983), 1983 (Box 11)
- 1983 Financial Report (January-November 1983), 1983-01-1983-11 (Box 11)
- Australian Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 12)
- AI General, Date unknown (Box 12)
- AI 1988 Action DC, 1988 (Box 12)
- Amnesty International on the Vigilantes 1987 Reports, 1987 (Box 12)
- Amnesty International Clippings, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Amnesty International Press Coverage, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Asian Pacific People's Conference, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Ramsey Clark, et al, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Committee to Protect Journalists, Date unknown (Box 12)
- European Initiative Against Human Rights Violations in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 12)
- EMJP, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Free Legal Assistance Group, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Human Rights Watch, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Humanities Law Project, Date unknown (Box 12)
- ICJ, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Internet, Date unknown (Box 12)
- HURIDOCS, Date unknown (Box 12)
- International Human Rights Law Group, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Lawyers Committee for International Human rights (LCIHR), Date unknown (Box 12)
- Mendiola Commission, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Northern Luzon Human Rights Organization, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Promotion of Church People's Rights (PCPR) Phil. Mission to UN, Date unknown (Box 12)
- PAHRA, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Philippine House Committee on People's Organizations Hearings, June 1, 1988, 1988-06-01 (Box 12)
- Presidential Committee on Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Presidential Commission on Human Rights - Mary Concepcion Bautista, Date unknown (Box 12)
- State Dept. HR, Date unknown (Box 12)
- SELDA, Date unknown (Box 12)
- TFD Comparative Statistics 1987 Summary 88 Jan-June, 1987-01-1987-06 (Box 12)
- TFD: Mindanao, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Human Rights Reports 1986, 1986 (Box 12)
- TFD Reports Feb-Sept 1986, 1986-02-1986-09 (Box 12)
- UCC-OCIS/UCBWM Vigilante Action Alert, Date unknown (Box 12)
- UCCP Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 12)
- VEMJP, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Alsa Masa, Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Vigilantes-Visayas, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Women Victims Feb 86-Feb 88/Gabriela commission on HR, 1986-02-1988-02 (Box 12)
- International Tribunal, Date unknown (Box 12)
- "Dramatic Increase in Philippine Human Rights Abuses", Date unknown (Box 12)
- Comprehensive List June 8-July 18, 1988, 1988-06-08-1988-07-18 (Box 12)
- Amnesty Int'l Dec 15, 1988 Reports on Torture, 1988-12-15 (Box 12)
- Cuanes Urgent Action, Date unknown (Box 12)
- CT for Chilian Inq, Date unknown (Box 12)
- TFD UA 1988, 1988 (Box 12)
- FFP Urgent Action Edwin Laguerder 87-9, 1987 (Box 12)
- 87-8 Dr Nemesio Prudente, etc, 1987 (Box 12)
- 87-7 Military Raids on Urban Poor Communities, 1987 (Box 12)
- Leandro Alejandro, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Congress Alert 87--6 US Role in Vigilante Violence, 1987 (Box 12)
- Bombing of Bishop Fortich's House, Date unknown (Box 12)
- 87-3 Peter Alderite, 1987 (Box 12)
- Negro farmer's arrests, burying of houses, killing, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Congress Alert Solarz Subcommittee hearing, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Mendiola Massacre, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Lupao Massacre, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Telexes from the Philippines 87, 1987 (Box 12)
- Telexes to the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Telexes from the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 12)
- July 18 "Update on Recent Human Rights Cases" CCHRP, Date unknown (Box 12)
- 88-17 Family Members killed by bombing, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-16 Evacuees killed, disappeared, 1988 (Box 12)
- UA 88-15 leftwing Youthleaders, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-14 Labor Leaders, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-13 Update, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-12 Jorge Madlos, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-10/88-11 Noel Villalba Action Taken, 1988-10 (Box 12)
- 88-11 N. Villalbe Update Hunger Strike, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-10 Noel Billalbe, 1988 (Box 12)
- UA 88-8 Surigao, 1988 (Box 12)
- Prudente 88-9, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-7 UA Germana Pastor etc, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-6 Human Rights Lobby Alert, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-5 Raid on Dante's House, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-4 Hilario Bustamente Rey Francisco, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-3 Abductions, Killings, 1988 (Box 12)
- 88-2 4 farmers arrested, 1 killed, 1988 (Box 12)
- Sister Vivian Beromal, Date unknown (Box 12)
- Final Address = Sr. Mariani D., Date unknown (Box 13)
- "Cry of the People - challenge to the churches" - Bishop Babayen, Date unknown (Box 13)
- "The Philippines: Where Vultures Gather" - PV Salgado, Date unknown (Box 13)
- "The Philippines: A challenge to the churches" - W. Howard, Date unknown (Box 13)
- An Asian Viewpoint, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Counterinsurgency + the US Bases, Date unknown (Box 13)
- I. Doctrine of National Security, Military Strategic Considerations, Date unknown (Box 13)
  Working Groups
- II. Militarism and Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 13)
- III. Economic Causes of Militarism and Violations of Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 13)
- IV. Ecumenical Solidarity and Networking, Date unknown (Box 13)
- V. Implications for the Churches, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Philippines: A Challenge to Churches in the USA, Date unknown (Box 13)
  Handouts
- Message of the IECP, Date unknown (Box 13)
- International Ecumenical Conference Statement, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Militarization of Asian Politics, by Jose W. Diokno, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Philippine Political Detainees: Living Evidences of Repression, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The United States-and the US Transnational Corporations-Finds the Philippines the El Dorado of its Gunboat Dreams, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Filipino Youth and Students in Active Response to the Problems of Campus and Society by League of Filipino Students, Date unknown (Box 13)
- United States Role on Militarization and Intervention in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Militarization Trends in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Box of conference papers, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Exploiting the Rich Land, Date unknown (Box 13)
- To the brothers and sisters gathered during the Sept…, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Filipino Peasantry: a History of Suffering and Hope, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Keeping the Wages Low and the Workers in Line, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Philippine Media, Date unknown (Box 13)
- In Sickness and in Health, but Always in Sickness, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Philippines in Global Perspective by Dolf Hautvast, KSP, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Philippines: The Case for International Ecumenical Solidarity, by Victor W.C. Hsu, Date unknown (Box 13)
- A Liturgy of Solidarity with the Filipino People, Date unknown (Box 13)
- A Prayer for Solidarity, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Towards a People's Church, by Bishop Erme Camba, UCCP, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Not Anymore for Gold by God, Glory, and Country, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Challenges to the Churches, by Louie G. Hechanova, CSSR, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Filipino Woman has a Decisive Role in Changing Society, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Message of Political Detainees to the IECP, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Filipino Teachers and the State of Philippine Education under the US Marcos Dictatorship, Date unknown (Box 13)
- The Military Implications of Anzus, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Papers on Ethnic Minorities in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous handouts, Date unknown (Box 13)
- Phil. Church Statements 1990, 1990 (Box 14)
- Philippine Church Statements 1989, 1989 (Box 14)
- Philippine Church Statements 1988, 1988 (Box 14)
- Philippine Church Statements 1987, 1987 (Box 14)
- US Church Statements 1990, 1990 (Box 14)
- US Church Statements 1989, 1989 (Box 14)
- US Church Statements (Canada) 1988, 1988 (Box 14)
- US Church Statements 1987, 1987 (Box 14)
- US Church Statements 1986, 1986 (Box 14)
- Church Resolutions 1975-1986, 1975-1986 (Box 14)
- 1991 Sustainable Peace Campaign, 1991 (Box 14)
- 1991 Consultation and Lobby Day, 1991 (Box 14)
- 1991 Originals of Resource Packet, 1991 (Box 14)
- NECP 1991-Originals of Packet Materials, 1991 (Box 14)
- 1991 NECP-Worship, 1991 (Box 14)
- 1991 NECP Envisioning the Future Workshop, 1991 (Box 14)
- Filipinos and US Americans: Forging a New Relationship in Support of a Sustainable Peace, Date unknown (Box 14)
- 1990 NECP Follow Up Mailing (4 copies), 1990 (Box 14)
- 1990 NECP Planning, 1990 (Box 14)
- Philippine Week 1990, 1990 (Box 14)
- "Beating Swords into Plowshares: toward a Sustainable Peace", Date unknown (Box 14)
- May 14, 1990 News conference on Bases, 1990-05-14 (Box 14)
- US Military Bases: Time to Go May 14, 1990, 1990-05-14 (Box 14)
- A Consultation on US Policy Toward the Philippines and Philippine Lobby Day March 12-13, 1990, 1990-03-12-1990-03-13 (Box 14)
- 1990 NECP Campaign Families Fleeing War, 1990 (Box 14)
- 1990-Consultation and Lobby Day, 1990 (Box 14)
- 1989 Events, 1989 (Box 14)
- 1989 NECP-Overseas correspondence concerning Campaign NECP 1989-Program, 1989 (Box 14)
- 1989 National Ecumenical Conf. on the Philippines (2 folders), 1989 (Box 14)
- NECP 1989 Mobilization/Outreach, 1989 (Box 14)
- 1989 Lobby Day with Consultation, 1989 (Box 14)
- Philippine Lobby day/consultation 3/15-17 1989, 1989-03-15-1989-03-17 (Box 14)
- 1989 Consultation and Lobby Day, 1989 (Box 14)
- 1989 Campaign - Families Fleeing War, 1989 (Box 14)
- 1989 Nat. Ecumenical Conf. on the Phil. 11/10-12 (2 copies), 1989-11-10-1989-11-12 (Box 14)
- Philippine Human Rights Lobby Day 4/28 1988, 1988-04-28 (Box 14)
- A Consultation on Paramilitary Violence and US Policy Toward the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 14)
- 1988 Lobby Day, 1988 (Box 14)
- 1988 Consultation Day, 1988 (Box 14)
- NECP 1988-National Mobilization, 1988 (Box 14)
- 1988 NECP, 1988 (Box 14)
- NECP 1988-Program, 1988 (Box 14)
- NECP 1988-Agendas/Minutes, 1988 (Box 14)
- NECP 1988 (2 copies), 1988 (Box 14)
- NECP 1988 Registration, 1988 (Box 14)
- NECP 1988-Contacts, 1988 (Box 14)
- 1988-Letter to Presidential Candidates, 1988 (Box 14)
- Flyers-1988 Events, 1988 (Box 14)
- National Campaign to End Vigilante Violence, Date unknown (Box 14)
- Evaluation of 1988 Vigilante campaign, 1988 (Box 14)
- 1988 Vigilante campaign, 1988 (Box 14)
- 1988 Consultation on US Policy Toward the Philippines 1/22/88, 1988-01-22 (Box 14)
- A Consultation on Challenging US Policy Towards the Philippines: the role of the church March 13, 1987, 1987-03-13 (Box 14)
- 1987 Consultation, 1987 (Box 14)
- NECP 1987 Pre-Conference Mailings NECP 1987, Documents, 1987 (Box 14)
- NECP 1987 Minutes/Program Guidelines, 1987 (Box 14)
- NECP 1987 Evaluations, 1987 (Box 14)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines November 13-15, 1987 Berkeley California, 1987-11-13-1987-11-15 (Box 14)
- NECP 1986 Conference Report Documents, 1986 (Box 14)
- Philippines Information Packet National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines Nov 22-23 1985, 1985-11-22-1985-11-23 (Box 14)
- NECP flyers (in US), Date unknown (Box 14)
- 10th Annual NECP: The Philippines in the Asia/Pacific Context: Challenges for US Solidarity work 12/2-4, 1994, 1994-12-02-1994-12-04 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Resolution to Clinton, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Packet Materials, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Registration, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Mobilization/Publicity, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP Worship, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Regional Meetings, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Network Celebration, 1993 (Box 14)
- 1993 NECP-Charles Meconis, 1993 (Box 14)
- 9th Annual NECP: Weaving a Vision for US-Philippine Solidarity Work 11/5-7, 1993, 1993-11-05-1993-11-07 (Box 14)
- 1992 NECP Campaign: Sustainable Peace, 1992 (Box 14)
- 1992 NECP-Transcripts, 1992 (Box 14)
- 1992 NECP-Packet Materials, 1992 (Box 14)
- 1992 NECP-Workshop Ideas, 1992 (Box 14)
- 8th Annual NECP: Claiming our Voices in the Wilderness…, Date unknown (Box 14)
- 1991 NECP Packet Materials, 1991 (Box 14)
- Sustainable Peace Resource Packet, Date unknown (Box 14)
- Filipinos and US Americans: Forging a New Relationship in Support of a Sustainable Peace Consultation and Lobby Day April 15-16, 1991, 1991-04-15-1991-04-16 (Box 14)